

Bachelor of Engineering with 6.5+ years of Total experience and 4+ years of experience in Pega Robotics(Open Span)



Current Designation: RPA Developer- Pega Robotics

Current Company: Cigna

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Pega Robotics, OpenSpan

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Summary

Overall 6+ Years of experience, having 4+ Years of experience in Robotic Process Automation Development using Open Span (Pega Robotics)

2 years of Experience in Quality Assurance

Strong Experience in VBA and C#.Net coding

Strong and precise understanding of Pega Open span Studios Windows/Web/Text adapters

Developed Automations on based as well as Mainframe based Automations

Experience in Troubleshooting and Debugging Pega Open span automations for bug fixes

Strong ability to convert business logic/requirements to automations

Responsible for development of business object and process for web based, windows-based applications.

Ability to work well in both team environment and individual environment.

Provide status updates to reporting manager in regular basis.

Experienced in Customer Quality. Handled all RMAs returns from Customer

Hands on Experience in in SAP, Oracle, Baan and Agile

Good knowledge in Agile Methodologies

Basic knowledge in PEGA PRPC

Work Experience

Cigna as RPA Developer- Pega Robotics Oct 2020 to Till Date

- ? Understand requirements given by site
- ? Analyze the feasibility of existing process suitable for operation
- ? Designing, Developing and Testing BOTs for process Pega Robotics
- ? Following Agile Methodologies Sprint planning and regular Retrospection meeting
- ? Develop processes and objects using core principles that are efficient, well structured, maintainable and easy to understand.
- ? Automate different applications from end to end
- ? Involved in preparing process related documents and status report
- ? Attending conference calls with site
- ? Created and Document Standard procedures
- ? Work with different Teams and Identify the areas to Automate
- ? Daily updates on the progress of the project.
- ? Conduct Regular Internal Audits

Thirdware Technologies as Technical Specialist -RPA

Nov 2019 to Oct 2020

Understand requirements given by site

Analyze the feasibility of existing process suitable for operation

Designing, Developing and Testing BOTs for process Pega Robotics

Following Agile Methodologies Sprint planning and regular Retrospection meeting

Develop processes and objects using core principles that are efficient, well structured, maintainable and easy to understand.

Automate different applications from end to end

Involved in preparing process related documents and status report

Attending conference calls with site

Created and Document Standard procedures

Work with different Teams and Identify the areas to Automate

Daily updates on the progress of the project.

Conduct Regular Internal Audits

Flex Ltd (previously known as Flextronics) as Engineer

Mar 2014 to Nov 2019

Understand requirements given by site

Analyze the feasibility of existing process suitable for operation

Designing, Developing and Testing BOTs for process Pega Robotics

Following Agile Methodologies Sprint planning and regular Retrospection meeting

Develop processes and objects using core principles that are efficient, well structured, maintainable and easy to understand.

Automate different applications from end to end

Involved in preparing process related documents and status report

Attending conference calls with site

Created and Document Standard procedures

Work with different Teams and Identify the areas to Automate

Daily updates on the progress of the project.

Conduct Regular Internal Audits

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Anna University in 2013

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C#.NET	2019	2020	2 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
OpenSpan (Pega Robotics)	19.1	2020	4 Year(s)
VBA		2020	6 Year(s)
MS EXCEL			
SAP			
Oracle			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Tamil				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Category: OBC - non-creamy

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time